<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>WWW-DB CS</title>
	<atom:link href="http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:40:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Taylor Swift, Beyonce reporting jobs trigger controversy</title>
		<link>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/taylor-swift-beyonce-reporting-jobs-trigger-controversy/</link>
					<comments>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/taylor-swift-beyonce-reporting-jobs-trigger-controversy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/?p=18</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s rare for a news outlet to dedicate a reporter to one personality, but the publication USA Today has decided Taylor Swift and Beyonce are phenomena requiring their own beats. The recent announcement by Gannett, which owns USA Today, that it was seeking two journalists to cover the biggest names in music as if they ... <a title="Taylor Swift, Beyonce reporting jobs trigger controversy" class="read-more" href="http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/taylor-swift-beyonce-reporting-jobs-trigger-controversy/" aria-label="More on Taylor Swift, Beyonce reporting jobs trigger controversy">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s rare for a news outlet to dedicate a reporter to one personality, but the publication USA Today has decided Taylor Swift and Beyonce are phenomena requiring their own beats.</p>
<p>The recent announcement by Gannett, which owns USA Today, that it was seeking two journalists to cover the biggest names in music as if they were running for president triggered both excitement and eyerolls &#8212; and broader conversation about coverage priorities in an increasingly fragmented and financially precarious news media environment.</p>
<p>Gannett, which owns more than 200 daily newspapers, has slashed jobs across local markets over the past several years, laying off six per cent of its news division in December. So news of the Tay and Bey positions struck a nerve.</p>
<p>&#8220;I suppose now is a good time to remind Twitter that I&#8217;m the only full-time news reporter left at my newspaper that was sold by Gannett in December,&#8221; said Brad Vidmar on X, the platform formerly known as Twitter.</p>
<p>Vidmar, 41, works for The Hawk Eye, a newspaper in Burlington, Iowa that GateHouse, an investment firm-run publishing company, purchased in late 2016.</p>
<p>In 2019 GateHouse acquired Gannett and took its name, becoming the largest newspaper company in the nation &#8212; and one with a reputation for scooping newspapers before curtailing their resources.</p>
<p>Gannett resold The Hawk Eye to a family-owned media company in late 2022 &#8212; its staff a skeleton of what it once was.</p>
<p>&#8220;They just kept cutting and cutting and cutting staff all across the board,&#8221; Vidmar told AFP. &#8220;What you saw was a situation where there are fewer reporters, reporters forced to take on multiple beats.&#8221;</p>
<p>Losing local content meant filling the paper with wire stories or stories from the broader USA Today network, he explained. Vidmar said Gannett&#8217;s announcement of the Swift job made &#8220;my eyes roll.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;They&#8217;ve been downsizing newsrooms for years now, but of course they need somebody dedicated to covering Taylor Swift,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>&#8216;Shaping a generation&#8217;<br />
Gannett said the new positions will be employed by USA Today and The Tennessean, the company&#8217;s Nashville-based paper.</p>
<p>The aim of the new jobs &#8212; which are in addition to three music reporters The Tennessean now employs &#8212; will be to &#8220;capture the excitement around Swift&#8217;s ongoing tour&#8230; while also providing thoughtful analysis of her music and career,&#8221; Gannett said. Another position is aimed at similarly analysing Beyonce&#8217;s impact.</p>
<p>The NewsGuild&#8217;s New York branch was skeptical, writing on X: &#8220;Gannett&#8217;s strategy to be profitable again: 1) Lay off hundreds of reporters 2) Destroy local news coverage 3) Hire a Taylor Swift reporter.&#8221;</p>
<p>Lark-Marie Anton, Gannett&#8217;s chief communications officer, said in a statement to AFP that &#8220;these roles do not come at the expense of other jobs,&#8221; noting that in Gannett&#8217;s bid to &#8220;grow our audience&#8221; the company has hired 225 journalists since March and has more than 100 open roles.</p>
<p>&#8220;Taylor Swift and Beyonce Knowles-Carter are artists and businesswomen. Their work has tremendous economic impact and societal significance influencing multiple industries and our culture &#8212; they are shaping a generation,&#8221; Anton said.</p>
<p>Under pressure<br />
Robert Thompson, a media scholar at Syracuse University, said his initial reaction to the new jobs was questioning whether &#8220;this is a joke.&#8221;</p>
<p>But he said after more reflection &#8220;I think it would be silly to categorically dismiss this&#8230; There are so few things that everybody really kind of knows whether they&#8217;re fans or not, and Beyonce and Taylor Swift are some of the very rare ones.&#8221;</p>
<p>The jobs have the potential to allow for &#8220;really insightful ways to tell the story of 21st-century America through the lens of its most popular personages,&#8221; he said.</p>
<p>On the other hand, Thompson acknowledged that negative reaction to the new jobs in light of dwindling local news coverage is reasonable.</p>
<p>&#8220;If you were to get a bunch of people together and say, &#8216;We&#8217;ve got X number of dollars, how should they be spent?&#8217; Most of them would probably not say the Taylor Swift beat,&#8221; he said</p>
<p>&#8220;But that doesn&#8217;t mean that separate from that context there can&#8217;t be some really good things to come of it.&#8221; If performed correctly, the new jobs are not necessarily the &#8220;dream&#8221; careers some headlines have touted them as, he said.</p>
<p>The fan bases for both Swift and Beyonce are notoriously defensive &#8212; music critics who make even the slightest negative comment about their idols can be doxxed or receive death threats. And along with the &#8220;organised wrath&#8221; of Swifties and the Beyhive, the worlds these artists have curated are famously guarded.</p>
<p>Plus, Thompson noted, &#8220;the eyes of the profession are going to be on these poor folks when they finally get hired. That first piece that they file &#8212; it better be really good.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/taylor-swift-beyonce-reporting-jobs-trigger-controversy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ranveer Singh to feature in ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023 anthem</title>
		<link>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/ranveer-singh-to-feature-in-icc-mens-cricket-world-cup-2023-anthem/</link>
					<comments>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/ranveer-singh-to-feature-in-icc-mens-cricket-world-cup-2023-anthem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:39:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bollywood actor Ranveer Singh is all set to feature in the official anthem of the ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023. Titled ‘Dil Jashn Bole’ the anthem is composed by music composed Pritam. Taking to X (formerly known as Twitter) the International Cricket Council (ICC) shared the first poster of the anthem. ICC wrote, “The ... <a title="Ranveer Singh to feature in ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023 anthem" class="read-more" href="http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/ranveer-singh-to-feature-in-icc-mens-cricket-world-cup-2023-anthem/" aria-label="More on Ranveer Singh to feature in ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023 anthem">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bollywood actor Ranveer Singh is all set to feature in the official anthem of the ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023.<br />
Titled ‘Dil Jashn Bole’ the anthem is composed by music composed Pritam.<br />
Taking to X (formerly known as Twitter) the International Cricket Council (ICC) shared the first poster of the anthem.<br />
ICC wrote, “The greatest cricketing Jashn is almost here, 12:00pm IST tomorrow! #CWC23.”</p>
<p>The poster features actor Ranveer Singh donning a maroon suit. He accessorized his look with a matching hat and shades.<br />
The official anthem of ICC Men’s Cricket World Cup 2023 will be out on 20 September.<br />
The World Cup will begin on 5 October with a match between England and New Zealand in Ahmedabad and the final will be played on 19 November. India will start its campaign with a match against Australia in Chennai on 8 October. India will also play arch-rivals Pakistan on 14 October at Ahmedabad.</p>
<p>Ten teams will feature in the biggest Cricket World Cup which will be played across 10 venues. Netherlands and Sri Lanka earned their way into the event through qualifiers.</p>
<p>However, it will be the first time that two-time champions West Indies will be missing this event.</p>
<p>The event will have 48 matches in 46 days.<br />
Indian squad for World Cup: Rohit Sharma (Captain), Shubman Gill, Virat Kohli, Shreyas Iyer, KL Rahul, Ishan Kishan, Suryakumar Yadav, Hardik Pandya (vice-captain), Ravindra Jadeja, Axar Patel, Shardul Thakur, Jasprit Bumrah, Kuldeep Yadav, Mohammed Shami, Mohammed Siraj.<br />
Talking about Ranveer’s work front, he will be next seen in director Farhan Akhtar’s next action thriller film ‘Don 3’.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/ranveer-singh-to-feature-in-icc-mens-cricket-world-cup-2023-anthem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joe Jonas reacts after ex-wife Sophie Turner sues him for custody of their children</title>
		<link>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/joe-jonas-reacts-after-ex-wife-sophie-turner-sues-him-for-custody-of-their-children/</link>
					<comments>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/joe-jonas-reacts-after-ex-wife-sophie-turner-sues-him-for-custody-of-their-children/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[American singer-songwriter and actor Joe Jonas has filed a response to Sophie Turner&#8217;s lawsuit alleging wrongful retention of the couple&#8217;s two children. A spokesman for the musician, 34, in a statement obtained by PEOPLE on Thursday responded to his estranged wife&#8217;s lawsuit which alleged that Jonas was refusing to let the couple&#8217;s two children, Willa, ... <a title="Joe Jonas reacts after ex-wife Sophie Turner sues him for custody of their children" class="read-more" href="http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/joe-jonas-reacts-after-ex-wife-sophie-turner-sues-him-for-custody-of-their-children/" aria-label="More on Joe Jonas reacts after ex-wife Sophie Turner sues him for custody of their children">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>American singer-songwriter and actor Joe Jonas has filed a response to Sophie Turner&#8217;s lawsuit alleging wrongful retention of the couple&#8217;s two children.</p>
<p>A spokesman for the musician, 34, in a statement obtained by PEOPLE on Thursday responded to his estranged wife&#8217;s lawsuit which alleged that Jonas was refusing to let the couple&#8217;s two children, Willa, 3, and 14-month-old daughter return to England.</p>
<p>“After multiple conversations with Sophie, Joe initiated divorce proceedings in Florida, as Florida is the appropriate jurisdiction for the case. Sophie was aware that Joe was going to file for divorce.</p>
<p>The Florida Court has already entered an order that restricts both parents from relocating the children. Sophie was served with this order on 6 September, 2023, more than two weeks ago,&#8221; the statement obtained by PEOPLE read.</p>
<p>“Joe and Sophie had a cordial meeting this past Sunday in New York when Sophie came to New York to be with the kids. They have been with her since that meeting. Joe’s impression of the meeting was that they had reached an understanding that they would work together towards an amicable co-parenting setup,&#8221; it read.</p>
<p>The statement asserted that the musician is &#8220;seeking shared parenting with the kids so that they are raised by both their mother and father and is, of course, also okay with the kids being raised both in the US and the UK,&#8221; but also alleges that the children &#8220;have spent the vast majority of their lives in the US&#8221;</p>
<p>“This is an unfortunate legal disagreement about a marriage that is sadly ending. When language like &#8216;abduction&#8217; is used, it is misleading at best, and a serious abuse of the legal system at worst. The children were not abducted,&#8221; the statement said.</p>
<p>&#8220;After being in Joe’s care for the past three months at the agreement of both parties, the children are currently with their mother,&#8221; it said. &#8220;Sophie is making this claim only to move the divorce proceedings to the UK and to remove the children from the US permanently.&#8221;</p>
<p>“Joe has already disavowed any and all statements purportedly made on his behalf that were disparaging of Sophie. They were made without his approval and are not consistent with his views. His wish is that Sophie reconsider her harsh legal position and move forward in a more constructive and private manner. His only concern is the well-being of his children,&#8221; the statement concluded.</p>
<p>The lawsuit against Jonas sought &#8220;the immediate return of children wrongfully removed or wrongfully retained,&#8221; with Turner&#8217;s legal team claiming the &#8220;wrongful retention&#8221; began on 20 September.</p>
<p>Turner claims she and the musician agreed to name England their &#8220;forever home&#8221; after chats during Christmas 2022 as they prepared for the coming year. After nearly three years of dating, the singer and the former Game of Thrones star married in 2019.</p>
<p>After four years of marriage, Jonas filed for divorce from the actress in September, according to records obtained by PEOPLE. According to the filing, &#8220;the marriage between the parties is irretrievably broken.&#8221; The records said that the children had recently moved home with their father.</p>
<p>“A parenting plan should be established, which addressed all parenting issues and contains a timesharing schedule providing for frequent and continuing contact with both parties,&#8221; the filing continued. &#8220;The children have been residing with their father in Miami and other locations throughout the United States.&#8221;</p>
<p>A source told People shortly after Jonas filed for divorce that the former couple&#8217;s children had more support living with the singer during their divorce. &#8220;She has been shooting which is why the kids have been with Joe. It&#8217;s just been easier because she&#8217;s been working for the kids to be with him because there&#8217;s some more support at home and on the road with his family. It’s something they both agreed was best.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/joe-jonas-reacts-after-ex-wife-sophie-turner-sues-him-for-custody-of-their-children/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8216;Wolverine&#8217; star Hugh Jackman and wife separating: statement</title>
		<link>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/wolverine-star-hugh-jackman-and-wife-separating-statement/</link>
					<comments>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/wolverine-star-hugh-jackman-and-wife-separating-statement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[‘Wolverine’ star Hugh Jackman and his wife of 27 years are to separate, a statement carried by US media said Friday. The Australian actor, 54, met fellow performer Deborra-Lee Jackman on the set of an Australian TV series in 1995, and the pair wed a year later. &#8220;We have been blessed to share almost (three) ... <a title="&#8216;Wolverine&#8217; star Hugh Jackman and wife separating: statement" class="read-more" href="http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/wolverine-star-hugh-jackman-and-wife-separating-statement/" aria-label="More on &#8216;Wolverine&#8217; star Hugh Jackman and wife separating: statement">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>‘Wolverine’ star Hugh Jackman and his wife of 27 years are to separate, a statement carried by US media said Friday. The Australian actor, 54, met fellow performer Deborra-Lee Jackman on the set of an Australian TV series in 1995, and the pair wed a year later.</p>
<p>&#8220;We have been blessed to share almost (three) decades together as husband and wife in a wonderful, loving marriage,&#8221; a joint statement first reported by People magazine said.</p>
<p>&#8220;Our journey now is shifting and we have decided to separate to pursue our individual growth. Our family has been and always will be our highest priority. We undertake this next chapter with gratitude, love, and kindness.&#8221; The couple has two children together.</p>
<p>Jackman, a Golden Globe winner for his role in ‘Les Miserables’, has juggled his image as a muscle-bound superhero, with ventures into music and dancing during a varied career.</p>
<p>&#8220;We greatly appreciate your understanding in respecting our privacy as our family navigates this transition in all of our lives,&#8221; the statement continues, adding that no further information will be released.</p>
<p>In a social media post to mark the couple&#8217;s silver wedding, Jackman described their marriage as &#8220;natural as breathing.&#8221;</p>
<p>&#8220;From nearly the moment we met&#8230; I knew our destiny was to be together. In our 25 years &#8211; our love has only grown deeper. I&#8217;m forever grateful to share our love, our life &#8211; and our family together. We&#8217;ve only just begun. Deb, I love you with all my heart!&#8221;</p>
<p>Jackman&#8217;s rippling muscles and cut-glass features have earned him an army of admirers, and in 2008 he was named People magazine&#8217;s ‘Sexiest Man Alive’.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://www-db.cs.wisc.edu/wolverine-star-hugh-jackman-and-wife-separating-statement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
